http://www.hydroponic-shop.com/site/privacy-policy.asp

0 items in your basket.
Grow Lamps - HID Lighting HPS / MH / CDM
Reflectors,
Ferro
G.A.S.
Privacy Policy
Welcome Guest (Login : Sign Up)
Username:
Password:
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Privacy Policy
Norfolk Lights & Hydroponics Centre are committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you.  We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection act in the UK.  The purpose of the statement is to explain to you our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
INFORMATION – COLLECTION AND USE:
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name such as, your e-mail address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, product selections, (credit card or other payment information - according to our terms and conditions). We only use this data for the following;
Processing your orders;
For statistical purposes, to improve the Site and its services to you;
To serve Site content and advertisements to you;
To administer the Site;
In relation to your preferences and email updates;
You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.
We will not contact you about promotions & new products, only in connection with a delivery. We can remove you from our database, if you so wish.
In order to effectively process credit or debit card transactions it may be necessary for the bank or card processing agency to verify your personal details for authorisation outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Such information will not be transferred out of the EEA for any other purpose.
You can confirm the security of your connection to the checkout page by checking the bottom of your browser window. When the connection is secure you will see a closed lock.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
We will never sell, rent, exchange or pass on your personal information to any third party, for any reason, beyond the essential card processing service that is required for validating a payment.
When you pay for your order online, please do so in the safe knowledge that all payments are subject to the latest encryption software with 128 bit SSL certificate.  We have no access to payment information, such as card details and these are not stored on our system.
We are compliant with The General Data Protection Regulation.  Our staff will destroy all information received in respect of a telephone order once the card details have been processed.  Your delivery address will be passed to only a reputable carrier, after ensuring that they are GDPR compliant too.
You have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address and payment of £2.95 to cover administration expenses to the following address:
Norfolk Lights & Hydroponics Centre LTD (Privacy)Unit 2, Guardian Road Industrial EstateNorwich, NorfolkNR5 8PF
Information
About Us
Hydroponics Blog
What is Hydroponics?
© 2018-2020, Norfolk Lights & hydroponics Centre Limited. All rights reserved.
Registered in England no: 05010464VAT no: 83 463 6123
website design diss by sla associates limited
